quizizz.com 2016-09-22

# Privacy Policy - Quizizz

#### Updated: February 1, 2015

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Quizizz, these our guiding principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of of our services.
  * We aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.

It is Quizizz's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.

This privacy statement describes how Quizizz collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site, Quizizz.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, Quizizz collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Quizizz’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Quizizz’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Quizizz may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Quizizz also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Quizizz does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to Quizizz's website choose to interact with Quizizz in ways that require Quizizz to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Quizizz gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at Quizizz to provide a username and email address. In all such cases, Quizizz collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with Quizizz. Quizizz does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally- identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Children

For all students, including children under 13, Quizizz offers a limited feature set and web site experience. We do not require students to submit their name or contact information. The only information we collect from students is a temporary nickname. The website also does not allow any type of direct communication to or between the student participants.

### Safety on Quizizz

Children’s safety and full enjoyment of Quizizz, as well as the safety and well being for all children and their families, is of the utmost importance to all of us at Quizizz. Quizizz does not accumulate personal information about any child or family for distribution, sharing, or selling except as described in this privacy policy.

### Aggregated Statistics

Quizizz may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. For instance, Quizizz may monitor the most popular quizzes on the Quizizz site. Quizizz may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Quizizz does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### How We Handle Personally Identifiable Information

Quizizz discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Quizizz's behalf or to provide services available at Quizizz's website and mobile applications, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Quizizz's website and mobile applications, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Quizizz will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Quizizz discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law such as to comply with a court order, or when Quizizz believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Quizizz, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a Quizizz website and have supplied your email address, Quizizz may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Quizizz and our products. We primarily use our product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Quizizz takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. You may choose to stop receiving our email by unsubscribing.

Name of Third Party Partner| What info is shared with or collected by this partner| Partner’s purpose| Link to Partner’s privacy policy  
---|---|---|---  
Amazon Web Services| Traffic data| Provider of servers and network infrastructure for basic service delivery| [AWS Privacy Policy](http://aws.amazon.com/privacy/)  
Google Inc. (Analytics)| Anonymous usage data (e.g., what pages on our site people visit.)| Analytics| [Google Analytics Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html)  
CleverTap| Anonymous usage data (e.g., what pages on our site people visit.)| Analytics| [CleverTap Privacy Policy](https://clevertap.com/privacy-policy/)  
Zendesk| Website Feedback and contact information.| User Feedback| [ZenDesk Data Policy](https://www.zendesk.com/company/privacy/)  
  
### Parental Rights

Parents and legal guardians of children under 13 who are members of Quizizz.com have certain rights under COPPA, and Quizizz recognizes those rights. Parents/guardians can consent to collection and use of a child's personally identifiable information (PII) without consenting to the disclosure of information to third parties. Currently the only identifiable information we collect from children under 13 is parent's email address.

Parents/guardians can review information their children have contributed to Quizizz.com, by accessing their child's account. Parents can also request that Quizizz delete that information and refuse to allow Quizizz to collect further information from their children by contacting us at contact@quizizz.com. Quizizz may ask additional questions or take other steps to verify the identity of parents/guardians before responding to a request to review or delete their child's information, or a request to refuse further collection from children.

A child's participation or access to an activity on Quizizz cannot be conditioned on him or her providing more information than is reasonably necessary for that activity, or any personally identifiable information. Quizizz does not collect personally identifiable information from children under 13, without a parent or guardian's consent.

### Study Set Discussion and Profile

Certain activity on Quizizz may be displayed to other users, such as posts to Quizizz discussion boards or our blog, or the information on your Quizizz Profile. This information includes your username and public quizzes created by you.

You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from these areas, contact us at contact@quizizz.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Quizizz uses cookies to help Quizizz identify and track visitors, their usage of Quizizz website, and their website access preferences. Quizizz visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies, but some of the Quizizz website’s features may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Web Beacons

Our Web pages contain third-party web beacons (electronic images sometimes called single-pixel gifs) which are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used.

### How to Update your Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may review, edit, or delete it on our Settings page. Parents may remove, delete or update an account or any information posted on Quizizz by contacting us at contact@quizizz.com.

### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at contact@quizizz.com.

### Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at contact@quizizz.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Contact Us

If you have questions or wish to send us comments about this Privacy Policy, please send an email to[ contact@quizizz.com](mailto:contact@quizizz.com), or write us at:

Quizizz Inc.  
2600 El Camino Real #403,  
Palo Alto, CA 94306

### Privacy Policy Changes

Quizizz reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we change how we use your personally identifiable information, we will notify, by email, and/ or by means of a notice on our Web site prior to the change becoming effective.
